{
  "inputTimeWaitSecs": 60,
  "questions": [
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(10 < 11\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.4 \\div 0.23\\)",
      "answer": "-40/23",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 115, 23]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{19}{20}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "361/400",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 400]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-0.12 > 2.1\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(2.2\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "121/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-29 \\div -0.2\\)",
      "answer": "145",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.5 - 0.001\\)",
      "answer": "499/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2000, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{23} \\div \\dfrac{9}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "20/69",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 207, 69]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{17}{16}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "289/256",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 256]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(2.9 > 0.12\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{28} \\div \\dfrac{15}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "13/60",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 420, 60]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.022\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "121/250000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 250000]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-0.021 \\leq 0.23\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{22}{5}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-22/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-5}{13} \\div \\dfrac{-3}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "145/39",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 39]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - 2.5\\)",
      "answer": "-5/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{4} \\leq 0.1\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{14}{23}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-14/23",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 23]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.26\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "169/2500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{4}{5}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.024 \\geq 0.002\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{7} - \\dfrac{1}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-2/35",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 35]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-29}{24} \\div \\dfrac{19}{18}\\)",
      "answer": "-87/76",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 456, 228, 152, 76]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.15 \\div 0.003\\)",
      "answer": "50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 60, 30, 20, 15, 12, 10, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{8} - \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-13/24",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 24]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-1 \\div \\dfrac{-8}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "5/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.027\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "729/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-2 > -1.4\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{10}{29}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "100/841",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 841]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{2} + 15\\)",
      "answer": "39/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(1 > \\dfrac{13}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{27}{28}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "729/784",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 784]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2.5 - 0.17\\)",
      "answer": "233/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 200, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{11} \\div \\dfrac{-11}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "-120/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.24 \\div 2.5\\)",
      "answer": "12/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-7 - \\dfrac{11}{24}\\)",
      "answer": "-179/24",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 24]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} - \\dfrac{12}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-17/14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 14]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10 \\div -0.003\\)",
      "answer": "-10000/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{1}{7}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/343",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 343]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-1 \\div \\dfrac{-9}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "26/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{15}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.026 \\div -0.17\\)",
      "answer": "-13/85",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0, 8500, 4250, 2125, 1700, 850, 425, 340, 170, 85
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{28} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "27/28",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 28]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-11}{2} \\div \\dfrac{-28}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "33/56",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 56]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{19}{6}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "361/36",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 36]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - 1\\)",
      "answer": "-1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{22}{9} \\div \\dfrac{3}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "638/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{15}{26} \\div 2\\)",
      "answer": "15/52",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 52]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{11} \\div \\dfrac{22}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "19/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 242, 121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-9 + 0.025\\)",
      "answer": "-359/40",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 40]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-27}{14} \\leq \\dfrac{20}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{23} + \\dfrac{-9}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-143/184",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 184]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(12 \\div 1.3\\)",
      "answer": "120/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{7} \\leq 1\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{8} + 2\\)",
      "answer": "21/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{13}{14}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "169/196",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 196]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-1.2 + -24\\)",
      "answer": "-126/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(14 - \\dfrac{1}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "69/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{14} - \\dfrac{13}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-83/154",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 154]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(2.7 < 0.6\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-19}{23} \\div \\dfrac{-29}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "266/667",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 667]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{4}{29}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "16/841",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 841]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-0.05\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/400",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 400]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{4} \\div \\dfrac{1}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "25/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{6} \\div \\dfrac{19}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "2/57",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 114, 57]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{23} - \\dfrac{13}{18}\\)",
      "answer": "-281/414",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 414]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-11}{15}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "121/225",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 225]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.012 \\div \\dfrac{-1}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-3/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 250, 125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.012 - 0.23\\)",
      "answer": "-109/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25000, 12500, 5000, 2500, 1000, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1.6 \\div -9\\)",
      "answer": "-8/45",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 45]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.011 - -0.11\\)",
      "answer": "99/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0, 100000, 50000, 25000, 20000, 10000, 5000, 4000, 2000, 1000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{6} + -3\\)",
      "answer": "-11/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{30}{11} \\div 1.1\\)",
      "answer": "300/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{27} + \\dfrac{14}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "131/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 81, 27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-10}{7} \\div \\dfrac{1}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-30/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{7} \\div \\dfrac{23}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "24/161",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 161]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{26} - \\dfrac{14}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "-339/650",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 650]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-28}{11} \\leq \\dfrac{16}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} < 0\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{8} < \\dfrac{4}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(2.4\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-12/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(18 = 0.1\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{28}{9} \\div \\dfrac{29}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "224/261",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 261]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{15}{23} \\div -2\\)",
      "answer": "-15/46",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 46]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.025 \\div 3\\)",
      "answer": "1/120",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 120]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{5} > \\dfrac{2}{21}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(3\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{9} \\div \\dfrac{11}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-2/33",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 99, 33]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-26}{9} \\div \\dfrac{-12}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "91/54",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 108, 54]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{16}{21} = \\dfrac{-25}{28}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{25}{7} + \\dfrac{12}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "509/119",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 119]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{11} + \\dfrac{25}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "321/22",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 22]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{13}{5}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-13/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-10}{27} + \\dfrac{28}{27}\\)",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 729, 243, 81, 27, 9, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.26 + 26\\)",
      "answer": "1313/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.7 \\div 30\\)",
      "answer": "7/300",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 300]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{17} > \\dfrac{7}{27}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{5} + \\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "27/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.006 + \\dfrac{15}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "7533/5500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.009\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "81/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{7} \\div \\dfrac{6}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "85/42",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 42]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{20} - \\dfrac{13}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-121/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 40, 20]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(1.8\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "81/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{30} + 21\\)",
      "answer": "643/30",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 30]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.14 \\div 0.04\\)",
      "answer": "7/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50, 10, 2]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-3}{2} > \\dfrac{1}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.29 \\div -0.08\\)",
      "answer": "-29/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 200, 40, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{19} + \\dfrac{29}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "614/133",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 133]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{10} > \\dfrac{-28}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{28} \\div \\dfrac{18}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "13/168",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 504, 168]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(12 \\div -21\\)",
      "answer": "-4/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 21, 7]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-0.002 < 18\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{17}{4}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "289/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 16]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.005 \\div 0.014\\)",
      "answer": "5/14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1400, 700, 350, 280, 140, 70, 56, 28, 14]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{17} \\div \\dfrac{-6}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "-125/51",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 102, 51]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{28}{15}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "784/225",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 225]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{3} - \\dfrac{26}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-68/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{19} < \\dfrac{9}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{3} \\div \\dfrac{5}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "76/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1.1 \\div 0.29\\)",
      "answer": "110/29",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 290, 145, 58, 29]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{7} \\div 0\\)",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": null
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-23 - 5\\)",
      "answer": "-28",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{9} + \\dfrac{12}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "833/225",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 225]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + \\dfrac{15}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "15/19",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 19]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{5} < \\dfrac{7}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(6\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(18 \\div 0.018\\)",
      "answer": "1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9, 3, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-11}{2}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "121/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{1}{3}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(-0.009\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "9/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2.5 \\div -1.5\\)",
      "answer": "-5/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-17}{27} + \\dfrac{18}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "299/297",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 297]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.08 \\div 0.023\\)",
      "answer": "80/23",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 575, 115, 23]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{28}{15}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-28/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.19 \\div -2.7\\)",
      "answer": "-19/270",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2700, 1350, 540, 270]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{16}{3} + 3\\)",
      "answer": "25/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.6 \\geq 0.02\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{7} \\div 9\\)",
      "answer": "2/63",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 63]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{10} + \\dfrac{11}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "131/70",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 70]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{12}{13} + \\dfrac{7}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "127/39",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 39]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{10} + \\dfrac{4}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "29/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-21}{26} - \\dfrac{21}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "-1029/598",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 598]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.02 \\div 0.013\\)",
      "answer": "20/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 650, 325, 130, 65, 26, 13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-6}{7} + \\dfrac{-10}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "-148/91",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 91]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.016 \\div -1.6\\)",
      "answer": "-1/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000, 500, 200, 100]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(4 \\leq \\dfrac{9}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-21}{17}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "441/289",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 289]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(10\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4} \\div \\dfrac{10}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "11/40",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 40]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{15} + \\dfrac{11}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "59/30",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 150, 30]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-19}{2} \\div \\dfrac{6}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "-247/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 12]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 - -10\\)",
      "answer": "11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{28}{3} \\div 0.21\\)",
      "answer": "400/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 63, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{23}{6}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-23/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-2}{13} \\div -2\\)",
      "answer": "1/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 26, 13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(2.1\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "441/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.23 < -29\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{10}{7}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-10/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{3} - \\dfrac{7}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "95/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 12]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{2} \\div \\dfrac{4}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-5/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-15 \\div 30\\)",
      "answer": "-1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 30, 10, 6, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.021\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "441/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{4} \\div \\dfrac{5}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "63/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.3 \\leq -0.017\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 \\div 24\\)",
      "answer": "1/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 24, 12]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.09 \\leq -0.19\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.28 - 0.18\\)",
      "answer": "1/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1250, 250, 50, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-17 + 0.07\\)",
      "answer": "-1693/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{20} \\div \\dfrac{23}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "21/46",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 460, 230, 92, 46]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{10} - \\dfrac{5}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "13/70",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 70]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{8}{17}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "64/289",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 289]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{16}{17} \\div 0.07\\)",
      "answer": "1600/119",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 119]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{20} \\leq \\dfrac{-9}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.014 \\div -0.03\\)",
      "answer": "7/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1500, 750, 375, 300, 150, 75, 60, 30, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(22\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-22",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-28 \\div 2.4\\)",
      "answer": "-35/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 12, 6, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.3 \\div 0.009\\)",
      "answer": "100/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 90, 45, 30, 18, 15, 9, 6, 3]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(26 \\geq \\dfrac{-13}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{13} + \\dfrac{17}{30}\\)",
      "answer": "341/390",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 390]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{16} + \\dfrac{-14}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "95/176",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 176]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{13} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "10/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{14}{13}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "196/169",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 169]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{11}{3}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "121/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(6\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "216",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.1 \\div 0.28\\)",
      "answer": "-5/14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 70, 14]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1.4 + 0.006\\)",
      "answer": "703/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2500, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(0.006\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-3/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-18}{7} \\div \\dfrac{13}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-18/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 91, 13]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{28} > \\dfrac{15}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-18\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "324",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-5}{4} - -2\\)",
      "answer": "3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-7}{2} - \\dfrac{11}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-23/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20, 10, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-4 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-13}{23} \\div \\dfrac{-22}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "325/506",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 506]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} - 0.05\\)",
      "answer": "17/60",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 60]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.25 \\div 0.014\\)",
      "answer": "125/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 28, 14, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.002 \\div 0.14\\)",
      "answer": "-1/70",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3500, 1750, 700, 350, 140, 70]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-1.6\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-512/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(29 \\div \\dfrac{3}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "203/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{25}{27}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "625/729",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 729]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-29}{17} + \\dfrac{11}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "100/51",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 51]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{5}{4}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "125/64",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 64]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.02 - 0.1\\)",
      "answer": "-2/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500, 250, 125, 100, 50, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-2}{13} - \\dfrac{15}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "-239/286",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 286]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-2}{3} + \\dfrac{21}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "17/69",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 69]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{1}{6}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/36",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 36]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-7}{4} - \\dfrac{8}{21}\\)",
      "answer": "-179/84",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 84]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{20}{11} - \\dfrac{22}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-62/99",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 99]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div \\dfrac{28}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 28, 14, 7, 4, 2, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-11}{4}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "121/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 16]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{29} - \\dfrac{11}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-299/116",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 116]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{9} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "-1/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-29}{3} - \\dfrac{2}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "-49/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 45, 15, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{17}{2}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "289/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.019 - 3\\)",
      "answer": "-2981/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2.3 \\div -0.25\\)",
      "answer": "-46/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{5} \\div \\dfrac{3}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "77/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{5} - \\dfrac{22}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "98/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{4}{7}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-4/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{12}{5} - \\dfrac{9}{20}\\)",
      "answer": "39/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100, 20]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.13 - 1.1\\)",
      "answer": "-123/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000, 500, 200, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(22\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "484",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{13} - \\dfrac{13}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "-64/195",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 195]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(3 \\geq \\dfrac{28}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{15}{23} + \\dfrac{5}{27}\\)",
      "answer": "520/621",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 621]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{24} \\div \\dfrac{10}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "29/80",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 240, 80]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{13}{2}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "169/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{30}{7} - \\dfrac{-8}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "506/105",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 105]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{15}{8} + \\dfrac{24}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "627/232",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 232]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.05 \\div 0.08\\)",
      "answer": "5/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 40, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.18 \\div 22\\)",
      "answer": "-9/1100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2} + 2\\)",
      "answer": "9/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-3}{23} + \\dfrac{-4}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-101/69",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 69]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{2}{25}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "4/625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 625]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{8} - -3\\)",
      "answer": "37/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{19} + \\dfrac{11}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "287/114",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 114]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(15 - \\dfrac{25}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "230/17",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 17]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4} + 0.1\\)",
      "answer": "7/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 40, 20]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} \\div \\dfrac{23}{20}\\)",
      "answer": "20/69",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 69]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(0.04\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-1/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.004 + \\dfrac{26}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "6503/750",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 750]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{23} \\div \\dfrac{1}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "168/23",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 23]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div \\dfrac{18}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 18, 9, 6, 3, 2, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{13}{29}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "169/841",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 841]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{3} \\div \\dfrac{-16}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "-437/48",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 48]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.15 \\div \\dfrac{11}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "-21/110",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 220, 110]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.09 - 0.19\\)",
      "answer": "-1/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0, 10000, 5000, 2500, 2000, 1250, 1000, 500, 400, 250, 200, 100, 80, 50,
        40, 20, 10
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.11 \\div 2.5\\)",
      "answer": "-11/250",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500, 250]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(30 - 8\\)",
      "answer": "22",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-9}{11} \\geq 10\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.026 \\geq -7\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{1}{9}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/729",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 729]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{26}{17} - \\dfrac{29}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-207/187",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 187]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.018 + 1.5\\)",
      "answer": "741/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.001 - \\dfrac{2}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "-403/3000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15000, 3000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{26}{27} \\div \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "13/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 54, 27, 18, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.02 - 1.1\\)",
      "answer": "-27/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500, 250, 125, 100, 50, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.013 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "13/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{15} \\div 0.013\\)",
      "answer": "2200/39",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 195, 39]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{18}{29} \\div \\dfrac{11}{27}\\)",
      "answer": "486/319",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 319]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-26}{3} + \\dfrac{4}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-118/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1.7 + 0.1\\)",
      "answer": "9/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100, 50, 25, 20, 10, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.05\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/400",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 400]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{21} \\div 2\\)",
      "answer": "23/42",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 42]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-18}{23} - \\dfrac{17}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "-733/437",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 437]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{26}{27} \\div 0\\)",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": null
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(1\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div \\dfrac{-2}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{29} - 1\\)",
      "answer": "-10/29",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 29]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-7}{26} \\div \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-21/52",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 52]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - 0\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{7} - \\dfrac{1}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "71/182",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 182]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-13 \\div 2.6\\)",
      "answer": "-5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13, 1]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-5}{14} < \\dfrac{22}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.03 - 5\\)",
      "answer": "-503/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-14}{5} + \\dfrac{17}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "-5/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 75, 15, 3]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(16 > -0.002\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1.5 \\div -0.7\\)",
      "answer": "-15/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 14, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.25 + 0.024\\)",
      "answer": "-113/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.016 \\div 2\\)",
      "answer": "1/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 250, 125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-9}{2} - \\dfrac{17}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "-205/38",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 38]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{3}{11}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "9/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{-1}{2}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} < \\dfrac{26}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{24} \\div 1\\)",
      "answer": "23/24",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 24]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{8} - \\dfrac{1}{16}\\)",
      "answer": "13/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 128, 64, 32, 16]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.016\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "4/15625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15625]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{18}{23} \\div \\dfrac{5}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "108/115",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 115]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{13} - 0.028\\)",
      "answer": "2159/3250",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3250]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{14}{17}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "196/289",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 289]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{5}{6}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "25/36",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 36]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.07 + 0.1\\)",
      "answer": "17/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000, 500, 200, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-13\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "169",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.2 - 1.4\\)",
      "answer": "-6/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.024\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "9/15625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15625]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{19} \\div \\dfrac{-7}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-136/133",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 133]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{28} - 3\\)",
      "answer": "-73/28",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 28]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "9/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{29} - \\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "19/58",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 58]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-0.25\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/64",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 64]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.28 + \\dfrac{-1}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "9/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 250, 50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-27}{8} \\div \\dfrac{11}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-27/22",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 88, 44, 22]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.18 + 0.009\\)",
      "answer": "-171/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50000, 25000, 10000, 5000, 2000, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{2} - \\dfrac{13}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "10/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 44, 22, 11]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{10} - \\dfrac{26}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-33/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{14}{17} \\div \\dfrac{9}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "196/153",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 153]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{18}{29} - \\dfrac{19}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-461/145",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 145]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.24 + 0.03\\)",
      "answer": "27/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2500, 500, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{5} \\div \\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "92/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(6 \\leq \\dfrac{23}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-12}{7} \\div \\dfrac{-30}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "26/35",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 210, 105, 70, 35]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{17} \\div -6\\)",
      "answer": "-1/102",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 102]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{3} \\div \\dfrac{17}{21}\\)",
      "answer": "56/17",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 51, 17]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{13} + 1\\)",
      "answer": "24/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.16 \\div 0.12\\)",
      "answer": "-4/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 75, 15, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(30 + \\dfrac{-3}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "687/23",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 23]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(2.5 < 0.02\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{28} + \\dfrac{-2}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "619/700",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 700]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.23 \\div -0.006\\)",
      "answer": "-115/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 300, 150, 75, 60, 30, 15, 12, 6, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{-1}{3}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-5}{13}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "25/169",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 169]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-19}{15}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "361/225",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 225]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{14}{3} \\div \\dfrac{22}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "161/33",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 66, 33]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2.5 - \\dfrac{29}{21}\\)",
      "answer": "47/42",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 42]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{12}{29} > 0.3\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(10\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{30} \\div \\dfrac{1}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "4/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 30, 15]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.2 < 0.029\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{22}{25} - \\dfrac{23}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "-3/650",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 650]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.27 \\div \\dfrac{-18}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "-39/200",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1800, 600, 200]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-9}{5}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "81/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{15} + \\dfrac{-21}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "-172/195",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 195]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{12} \\div \\dfrac{-3}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-35/36",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 36]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{26} < \\dfrac{-22}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.18 \\div 0.13\\)",
      "answer": "18/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 650, 325, 130, 65, 26, 13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{15}{17} + \\dfrac{3}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "201/170",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 170]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{16}{21} + -0.08\\)",
      "answer": "358/525",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 525]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{3}{16}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "9/256",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 256]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1.8 \\div -1\\)",
      "answer": "-9/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.011 - -0.19\\)",
      "answer": "201/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0, 100000, 50000, 25000, 20000, 10000, 5000, 4000, 2000, 1000
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-1.8 > 0.02\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{20} \\div \\dfrac{1}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20, 10, 4, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + -30\\)",
      "answer": "-30",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.18\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "81/2500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "5/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.026 \\div \\dfrac{-26}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-9/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13000, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{13} \\div 8\\)",
      "answer": "23/104",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 104]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.016 - 0.029\\)",
      "answer": "-13/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125000, 25000, 5000, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{3} \\div \\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "8/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-2.3 \\div \\dfrac{9}{20}\\)",
      "answer": "-46/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 90, 45, 18, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{23} \\div \\dfrac{24}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "13/552",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 552]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(10\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.27 - 14\\)",
      "answer": "-1373/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{29} - \\dfrac{29}{28}\\)",
      "answer": "-589/812",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 812]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-4}{3} + 0.02\\)",
      "answer": "-197/150",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 150]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{23} \\geq \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(2 \\leq \\dfrac{9}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.21 + -0.21\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0, 10000, 5000, 2500, 2000, 1250, 1000, 625, 500, 400, 250, 200, 125,
        100, 80, 50, 40, 25, 20, 16, 10, 8, 5, 4, 2, 1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.028 + 0.026\\)",
      "answer": "27/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0, 125000, 62500, 25000, 12500, 5000, 2500, 1000, 500
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-9}{2} \\div \\dfrac{15}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "-21/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 30, 15, 10, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{27} \\div \\dfrac{10}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "44/135",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 270, 135]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.9 \\div 0.25\\)",
      "answer": "18/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{3} - \\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "65/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 12]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-5}{3}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "25/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{28}{19}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-28/19",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 19]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 \\div \\dfrac{10}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "21/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.001 \\div -27\\)",
      "answer": "-1/27000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 27000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-7}{4} \\div \\dfrac{7}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-5/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 28, 14, 4, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{16}{3} - \\dfrac{13}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "67/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 45, 15]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.09 \\geq 1.4\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(25 \\div 0\\)",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": null
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.07 \\div 0.21\\)",
      "answer": "-1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0, 2100, 1050, 525, 420, 300, 210, 150, 105, 84, 75, 60, 42, 30, 21, 15,
        12, 6, 3
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(23\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "529",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(28 + 2.9\\)",
      "answer": "309/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{10} \\div 9\\)",
      "answer": "7/30",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 90, 30]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{6} + 1\\)",
      "answer": "13/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{5} \\div \\dfrac{-22}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-3/55",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 110, 55]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{-8}{15}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "8/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-2 - \\dfrac{2}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "-48/23",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 23]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-2.5 \\div 10\\)",
      "answer": "-1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(22\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "484",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.008 + -17\\)",
      "answer": "-2124/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{22}{29} < \\dfrac{15}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.026 \\div -0.004\\)",
      "answer": "13/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500, 250, 100, 50, 20, 10, 4, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{7}{10}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "49/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{5}{22}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "25/484",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 484]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-1.2 + 1.4\\)",
      "answer": "1/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{8} + -5\\)",
      "answer": "-37/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(16\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "256",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-0.08\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "4/625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 625]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(0.23\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-23/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.029 = 2.3\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{15}{2}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "225/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{13} \\div \\dfrac{10}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "12/65",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 130, 65]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-23}{10} \\div \\dfrac{-14}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "69/28",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 140, 28]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{20} - \\dfrac{7}{18}\\)",
      "answer": "11/180",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 360, 180]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.08\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "4/625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 625]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{4} < \\dfrac{3}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{9} - \\dfrac{7}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "-46/153",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 153]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} - \\dfrac{4}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-5/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-10}{9} \\div \\dfrac{-13}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "20/39",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 117, 39]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-6}{23}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "36/529",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 529]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-9}{14} \\div \\dfrac{28}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-99/392",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 392]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{11}{7}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "121/49",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 49]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(28 + -0.7\\)",
      "answer": "273/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{26}{29} \\div -19\\)",
      "answer": "-26/551",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 551]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-29}{16} \\div 1.4\\)",
      "answer": "-145/112",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 112]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{10} \\div \\dfrac{15}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "11/150",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 150]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{7} < \\dfrac{9}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-10}{11} \\div 26\\)",
      "answer": "-5/143",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 286, 143]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{5} + 13\\)",
      "answer": "74/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{6} - \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 12, 6, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.28\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "49/625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 625]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{25}{26} + 4\\)",
      "answer": "129/26",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 26]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(25 \\div 27\\)",
      "answer": "25/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{12} - \\dfrac{-29}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "173/36",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 108, 36]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.2 + 14\\)",
      "answer": "71/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{14}{11}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-14/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 11]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{6} \\div \\dfrac{2}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "65/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 12]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.001 - 28\\)",
      "answer": "-27999/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{17} + \\dfrac{-13}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-74/119",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 119]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{6} + \\dfrac{-6}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "211/78",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 78]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{11}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "5/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 11]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{13} \\geq \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{17} = \\dfrac{21}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.25 - 24\\)",
      "answer": "-95/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(6\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{7} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "29/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0 < -28\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{1}{3}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-24}{11} \\geq \\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{25}{23} \\div \\dfrac{8}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "175/184",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 184]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{28} \\div \\dfrac{-25}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "-323/700",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 700]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-5}{12} - \\dfrac{-11}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "107/60",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 60]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(2.7\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "729/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-2.2 \\div 0.007\\)",
      "answer": "-2200/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 35, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.14 - -0.007\\)",
      "answer": "147/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50000, 25000, 10000, 5000, 2000, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{17} \\div \\dfrac{12}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "77/204",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 204]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-0.03 < 0.2\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{22} \\div \\dfrac{4}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "377/88",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 88]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(30\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "900",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{21} + 0.013\\)",
      "answer": "2273/21000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 21000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-10 - 0.06\\)",
      "answer": "-503/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.004 \\div 0.12\\)",
      "answer": "1/30",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 750, 150, 30]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-9 \\div \\dfrac{15}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "-39/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.21\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "441/10000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-3 + \\dfrac{-5}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-11/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(29 \\div 0.03\\)",
      "answer": "2900/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{-5}{12}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "5/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 12]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{4} \\div \\dfrac{27}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "143/54",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 108, 54]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.05 \\div 30\\)",
      "answer": "1/600",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 600]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-13}{21} \\div \\dfrac{-1}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "26/21",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 21]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.009 - -0.002\\)",
      "answer": "11/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0, 500000, 250000, 125000, 100000, 50000, 25000, 20000, 10000, 5000,
        4000, 2000, 1000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{7}{8}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "343/512",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 512]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-2.8\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "196/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.24 \\div 0.024\\)",
      "answer": "10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 75, 25, 15, 5, 3, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{18} - \\dfrac{23}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "46/117",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 468, 234, 117]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-0.6 < 0.025\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{9}{11}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "81/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{11} \\div \\dfrac{14}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "87/77",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 154, 77]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-1}{4}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 16]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{14} > -6\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-16 \\div \\dfrac{23}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-48/23",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 23]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{5}{23}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "25/529",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 529]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1.9 - 0.07\\)",
      "answer": "183/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000, 500, 200, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-28}{23} \\div \\dfrac{16}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-49/92",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 368, 184, 92]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.17 \\div -2.5\\)",
      "answer": "-17/250",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500, 250]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-29 \\leq \\dfrac{17}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{13} - \\dfrac{16}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-118/117",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 117]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(-2.2\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "11/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{12}{17} \\div \\dfrac{15}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "104/85",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 255, 85]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + \\dfrac{13}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "13/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 12]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-14}{25}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "196/625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 625]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.01 \\div 0.013\\)",
      "answer": "10/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1300, 650, 325, 260, 130, 65, 52, 26, 13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-9}{16} \\div \\dfrac{21}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-15/112",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 336, 112]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{15} - \\dfrac{23}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "-22/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 225, 75, 45, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{25} \\div \\dfrac{2}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "207/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{17} \\div \\dfrac{-4}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-81/68",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 68]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div 20\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20, 10, 5, 4, 2, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{7} \\div \\dfrac{-15}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "-286/105",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 105]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{6} \\div \\dfrac{1}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6, 3, 2, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{16}{25}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "256/625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 625]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-7}{5} - \\dfrac{-30}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "73/55",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 55]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1.2 \\div 0\\)",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": null
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-6}{13}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "36/169",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 169]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{14} \\div \\dfrac{-2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-27/28",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 28]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-21}{13} - \\dfrac{8}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-335/143",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 143]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{26}{3} \\div \\dfrac{6}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "377/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 18, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.5 \\div 24\\)",
      "answer": "1/48",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 48]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{17} - \\dfrac{-18}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "762/323",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 323]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{15}{7}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "225/49",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 49]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(1\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-22 \\leq 21\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{15} + -9\\)",
      "answer": "-136/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-26 \\div 0.004\\)",
      "answer": "-6500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-27}{2}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "729/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-2\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{12}{11}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "144/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{4} - \\dfrac{17}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "37/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 32, 16, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div -3\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{9}{2}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-9/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.4 \\div 1.5\\)",
      "answer": "4/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.13 \\geq 0.23\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-23}{4}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "529/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 16]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-11}{3} - \\dfrac{-28}{27}\\)",
      "answer": "-71/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 81, 27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{3}{4}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "9/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 16]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{3}{29}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "9/841",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 841]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-0.1 > 3\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.022 \\div 0.03\\)",
      "answer": "11/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1500, 750, 375, 300, 150, 75, 60, 30, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{23} + \\dfrac{14}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "645/437",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 437]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{5} + \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "16/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.15 + 0.018\\)",
      "answer": "21/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0, 10000, 5000, 2500, 2000, 1250, 1000, 625, 500, 250, 125
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.7\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "343/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{27} + \\dfrac{-21}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-509/54",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 54]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{30}{11} - \\dfrac{7}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-17/22",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 22]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} \\div \\dfrac{-20}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "-17/60",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 60]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{8} - \\dfrac{19}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "-13/56",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 112, 56]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4} - \\dfrac{3}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "3/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.023 + -11\\)",
      "answer": "-10977/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(12 - \\dfrac{5}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "67/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.1\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-4}{7} \\div \\dfrac{20}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 140, 70, 35, 20, 10, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-11}{12} \\div \\dfrac{9}{16}\\)",
      "answer": "-44/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 108, 54, 27]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{5} < 0.28\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2} \\div \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "5/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(13 \\div 11\\)",
      "answer": "13/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 11]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{11} \\div \\dfrac{27}{16}\\)",
      "answer": "16/297",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 297]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{6} < \\dfrac{10}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{27} \\div \\dfrac{8}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "221/216",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 216]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{8} \\div \\dfrac{9}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "49/72",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 72]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{2} \\div 0\\)",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": null
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{13}{24}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "169/576",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 576]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.004 + -1.4\\)",
      "answer": "-349/250",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1250, 250]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-3}{4} \\div 1\\)",
      "answer": "-3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(1.4\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "343/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(13 \\div -0.2\\)",
      "answer": "-65",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{16} - \\dfrac{5}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-31/48",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 96, 48]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(15\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "225",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.04\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 625]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} > \\dfrac{29}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(-3\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{29} < 14\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(28 + 0.12\\)",
      "answer": "703/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-25}{3}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "625/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{8} - \\dfrac{28}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "327/232",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 232]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-19}{18} \\div \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-19/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 54, 27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-1}{5}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.01 \\div 0.19\\)",
      "answer": "1/19",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1900, 950, 475, 380, 190, 95, 76, 38, 19]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} - \\dfrac{7}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-10/33",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 33]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{6} < \\dfrac{9}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + \\dfrac{-17}{20}\\)",
      "answer": "-17/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.001\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(12 - 0.2\\)",
      "answer": "59/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-11}{27} + \\dfrac{17}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "250/513",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 513]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{10}{17}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "100/289",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 289]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 \\div \\dfrac{27}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "70/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{8} \\div 7\\)",
      "answer": "19/56",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 56]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{19} + \\dfrac{13}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "397/285",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 285]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.009 \\div 0.016\\)",
      "answer": "-9/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2000, 400, 80, 16]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(18 - -6\\)",
      "answer": "24",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 - \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "9/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + -12\\)",
      "answer": "-8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{8} + \\dfrac{5}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "43/24",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 96, 48, 24]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{25}{28}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "625/784",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 784]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{22}{27} \\div \\dfrac{25}{18}\\)",
      "answer": "44/75",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 675, 225, 75]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-8}{13} + \\dfrac{3}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-41/130",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 130]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2.9 \\div 0.003\\)",
      "answer": "2900/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 30, 15, 6, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div 25\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25, 5, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 - -0.12\\)",
      "answer": "203/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.024 \\div -1\\)",
      "answer": "-3/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - \\dfrac{25}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-25/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 11]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{16}{7} \\div \\dfrac{-15}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "-368/105",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 105]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5} \\div \\dfrac{4}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{-7}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "-15/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{12}{13} + \\dfrac{17}{30}\\)",
      "answer": "581/390",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 390]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 - \\dfrac{-9}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "19/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{12} + \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "31/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 24, 12]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-19}{6} \\div 4\\)",
      "answer": "-19/24",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 24]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{4} + \\dfrac{3}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "-7/52",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 104, 52]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{19}{11}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "361/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{26} \\div \\dfrac{19}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "69/494",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 494]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-0.3\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-27/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{13} + \\dfrac{5}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "81/52",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 52]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{21} > \\dfrac{3}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{2} \\div 1\\)",
      "answer": "7/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{19} = \\dfrac{1}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-11}{14} + \\dfrac{21}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "107/238",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 238]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.4 + 0.13\\)",
      "answer": "53/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.2 \\div 0.015\\)",
      "answer": "40/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.019 \\div 1\\)",
      "answer": "-19/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.025 = -0.11\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{26} + 20\\)",
      "answer": "539/26",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 26]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{18} \\leq \\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{15} + \\dfrac{22}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "101/75",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 375, 75]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{27} \\div 10\\)",
      "answer": "11/270",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 270]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 \\div \\dfrac{7}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "36/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.24 + 0.019\\)",
      "answer": "-221/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25000, 5000, 1000]
    }
  ]
}
